http://www.ckuk.com/privacy-statement

Contact/
CKUK Media Ltd Privacy StatementThe Data Controller for the Company is Christopher Kent, Director CKUK Media LtdThe Data Controller may be contacted at CKUK Media Ltd, The Courtyard, Selby Road, London, W5 LX. Tel: 020 8991 1855 Email: chris@ckuk.comData Subjects of the business:Clients, Business Contacts, Agents and Freelancers employedTypes of Personal Data include the following:Name, Trading Name, Telephone Number, Address, Email Address, Payment DetailsData Use:The Data is used to discuss business opportunities with former, repeat and new clients and to engage in negotiation, contractual agreement and fulfilment of any contracted services. It may also be used to update clients on working matters relating to CKUK Media LtdLawful BasisThe lawful basis identified for the processing of such data is Legitimate Business InterestsHow Data Is ObtainedAll Data is obtained directly from the Data Subjects listed aboveData SharingData is never shared with anyone other than the relevant Data Subject except under the instruction of or with the explicit agreement of the Data Subject or in order to comply with legal obligations.Data RetentionThe CKUK Media Ltd data retention policy is to review all data held on individuals at least every three years and remove data where we no longer have a legitimate reason to keep it.Where you have withdrawn your consent for us to use your data for a particular purpose (e.g. unsubscribed from a mailing list) we may retain some of your data for up to two years in order to preserve a record of your consent having been withdrawn.Data relating to payments and financial information which the company is obliged to retain to meet its legal obligations (such as HMRC) will be retained for the minimum period specified by the relevant Regulations (e.g. 6 years for HMRC).Security MeasuresThe Company, because of its size and the nature of its collection and use of data does not deem it necessary to use encryption. Almost all the data retained is readily available from public and other sources and the nature of the data is deemed to be extremely low risk in terms of harm or damage. The Company will protect data using appropriate protection software.We sometimes use third party services to process and store data (e.g. Quickbooks, Intuit, Google Drive, MS Outlook). We will always make sure any third parties we use are reputable, secure, and process your data in accordance with your rights under GDPR. We verify that whenever international data transfers are involved with any third party, these will be compliant with the GDPR requirement.What rights do you have?Under the GDPR, you have the following rights over your data and its use:·      The right to be informed about what data we are collecting on you and how we will use it·      The right of access – you can ask to see the data we hold on you·      The right to rectification – you can ask that we update or correct your data·      The right to object – you can ask that we stop using your data for a particular purpose·      The right to erasure – you can ask us to delete the data we hold on you·      The right to restrict processing – you can ask that we temporarily stop using your data while the reason for its use or its accuracy are investigated·      Though unlikely to apply to the data we hold and process on you, you also have rights related to portability and automated decision making (including profiling)All requests related to your rights should be made to the Data Controller Christopher Kent at chris@ckuk.com. We will respond within one month.You can find out more about your rights on the Information Commissioner’s Office websiteWhat will we do if anything changes?If we make changes to our privacy statements or processes we will post the changes here. Where the changes are significant, we may also choose to email individuals affected with the new details. Where required by law, will we ask for your consent to continue processing your data after these changes are made.
Home/
VO Studio/AboutGlobal AccessibilityLocationStudio rate card
VO Production/AboutVoice castingCase studies
Voice-overs by CK/
ODYSSEY/
News/
Contact/
CKUK Spoken Words
CKUK Media is the London based specialist voiceover recording and project management company.  We provide a multilingual voiceover production service to the international broadcast, advertising, film and multimedia industries, under the direction of leading British voice talent and actor Christopher Kent. Using cutting edge modern technology and one of the best sounding voice studios in London, CKUK delivers crystal clear digital audio to clients worldwide.
Biographies
Christopher Kent has appeared on stage, screen and radio in a wide range of roles from Shakespeare to contemporary drama. London theatre appearances have included Cyrano de Bergerac with Robert Lindsay at the Theatre Royal Haymarket and The Government Inspector with Timothy Spall at Greenwich Theatre. Chris is also one of the UK’s best known voiceover actors, regularly heard on commercials, documentaries, film trailers and literary recordings. His concert work includes collaborations with the Bridge String Quartet, Orlando Chamber Choir and West London Sinfonia.
Gamal Khamis studied at the Royal College of Music. He first performed at the Wigmore Hall at the age of ten, and has since appeared at most of the major UK concert halls, across Europe, the USA and Canada, and on BBC Radio 3 and Dutch radio. He has worked with leading composers including Thomas Adès and Mark Anthony Turnage and has been a Concordia Foundation Artist since 2010, a Park Lane Group Artist since 2013, and is a member of the Lipatti Piano Quartet.
CKUK Media LimitedLondon W5 1LX+44 20 8991 1855info@ckuk.com
Copyright © 2015 CKUK Media Ltd. All rights reserved.Terms & ConditionsPrivacy StatementPrivacy Statement
